

+45 50 30 01 92

peter.rambeck@me.com

www.indochinaexplorers.com

Peter Rambeck Andersen

Lyngby.

Danish 27 06 1969 Married

Linkedin Online CV https://www.linkedin.com/in/peter-rambeck-andersen/

http://www.peterrambeckandersen.com/en

PROFILE Independent.

Startup, from 2008 to 2019 I ran own highly specialised inbound travel agency from Bangkok, Thailand,

Vision in Motion:

In December 2008 I seized a marketing opportunity and started a new venture in Bangkok, Thailand. With own marketingbrand: 'Indochina Explorers', I converted my vision and businessplan into a range of specialised niche B2B travel inbound services, geographically covering destinations in Asia. I designed, created and marketed a comprehensive set of travel products and services from start to end.

Results:

I achieved great success with professional clients globally in business areas as: Educational tours for college students, custom made itineraries and special experience programs, extensive cycling trips, group travel, multi country combinations, MICE (Meetings, Incentives, Conference, Events) and luxury travel.

A short selection:

2009-2012 sole supplier for SAS (Scandinavian Airlines) Leisure in Thailand, Malaysia, Vietnam, China og Japan. // (SAS Leisure closed down in 2012.)

Supplier of educational tours in Vietnam for China Experience (DK), Sports / Educational for Bundabashers (SA) in Thailand and Japan, Custom made programs for Voya Travel's (DK) premium travellers. Corporate Incentives for Crown og Champa group's chain of luxury resorts. (Maldives)

SKILLS

Working with people

PRODUCT DEVELOPMENT:

Good understanding of segmented consumer needs and value creation.

OPERATION MANAGEMENT

Both as a self-employed and Area Manager in charge of the overall operation, - large-scale operation as specialised niche, development of business areas, managing teams and suppliers.

PROJECT MANAGEMENT

Rich experience from being part of many diverse projects.

Initiate projects with team planning and resource allocation.

As an initiator I'm used to work independently, able to drive a project and position myself in a key role whilst solemnly implementing a strategy with teams, and converting it into results

CUSTOMER EXPERIENCE

The end user's experience of product and service has always been pivotal in development as implementation.

DIGITIZED

Many years of commercial use and development of professional IT tools with supplementary studies.

EMPLOYMENT

2008 -2019 Founder

Indochina Explorers

Specialised inbound travel agency.

Startup. A business model covering the 'Indochina' region was started in partnership with local agency S.I. Tours (1996) for Thailand, as well as a network of local partners in Vietnam, Malaysia, Laos, Cambodia, China and Japan.

Under own marketing brand: Indochina Explorers, I contracted suppliers, product developed and marketed travel products and MICE services to travel agencies and corporations globally.

As part of the business model I developed a supplier network with the capability for extensive cycling programs, Educational & sport programs, premium experiences and more to support my global clients.

1996 - 2007 Area Manager (and more)

Thomas Cook Northern Europe.

Prior to my startup I had an extensive career with Thomas Cook Northern Europe, which took me through a great deal of functions and business areas in Denmark as well as internationally.

From handling ad planning large scale operations and leading teams in Thailand, Vietnam, Malaysia, India, Croatia, England, Egypt. -To tech project implementation as a strategic tool for HR capacity optimisation through a large organisation, Copenhagen. Holding various positions and managing different responsibilities over the period. Timeline: outline and specifications.

EDUCATION

2018 - 19 UNIVERSITY OF COPENHAGEN

Computer science course: Programming and Problem Solving (PoP)

Faculty of Science

2016 - 17 DATA SCIENCE & WEB DESIGN.

Coursera.org (John Hopkins uni. & Uni. of London) 8 MOOC Courses completed, part of 2 Specialisations

2008 EXECUTIVE MBA

ABAC, Assumption University, Bangkok. Fast track 7 months international MBA.

1998 - 2000 HD 1 DEL

Copenhagen Business School

Graduate Diploma Business Administration, HD 1.

1996 - 98 MERKONOM I MARKSFØRING

Copenhagen Business College,

Diploma, Niels Brok.

LANGUAGES

ENGLISH Profound. DANISH Native.

IT - SKILLS

PHP Several years of experience with Wordspress CMS HTML/CSS/JS Good understanding, Beginner to medium in coding.

ADOBE CC User experience.

OFFICE PACK Many years of user experience.



